Elvis had one chance to show the world he was still the King of Rock N’ Roll
Return of the King: The Fall and Rise of Elvis Presley is a
documentary, music film directed by Jason Hehir.
He had one chance to show the world he was still the King of Rock 'n' Roll.
Discover the story behind Elvis Presley's triumphant '68 comeback special.
Self (archive footage), played by Elvis Presley.
Self, played by Priscilla Presley.
Self, played by Darlene Love.
Self, played by Jerry Schilling.
Self, played by Bruce Springsteen.
Self, played by Billy Corgan.
Return of The King: The Fall and Rise of Elvis Presley is a documentary about Elvis
Presley's 1968 comeback special which debuted on Netflix on November 13, 2024.
The film explores themes of pop culture, us army,
biography, downfall, archive footage.
The tone is uplifting.